{
  "index": 1,
  "title": "한글 드릴",
  "data": [
    { "question": "ㅏ", "answer": ["아(ア)", "ア", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅣ", "answer": ["이(イ)", "イ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅜ", "answer": ["우(ウ)", "(口をすぼめて)ウ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅡ", "answer": ["으(ウ)", "(口を横に広げて)ウ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅐ", "answer": ["애(エ)", "エ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅔ", "answer": ["에(エ)", "エ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅓ", "answer": ["어(オ)", "(口を縦に広げて)オ", "母音"] },
    {
      "question": "ㅗ",
      "answer": ["오(オ)", "(唇を真ん中に集めて)オ", "母音"]
    },
    { "question": "ㅑ", "answer": ["야(ヤ)", "ヤ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅠ", "answer": ["유(ユ)", "ユ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "여", "answer": ["여(ヨ)", "(口を縦に広げて)ヨ", "母音"] },
    {
      "question": "ㅛ",
      "answer": ["요(ヨ)", "(唇を真ん中に集めて)ヨ", "母音"]
    },
    { "question": "ㅘ", "answer": ["와(ワ)", "ワ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅒ", "answer": ["얘(イェ)", "イェ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅖ", "answer": ["예(イェ)", "イェ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅟ", "answer": ["위(ウィ)", "ウィ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅢ", "answer": ["의(ウィ)", "ウィ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅙ", "answer": ["왜(ウェ)", "ウェ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅚ", "answer": ["외(ウェ)", "ウェ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅞ", "answer": ["웨(ウェ)", "ウェ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅝ", "answer": ["워(ウォ)", "ウォ", "母音"] },
    { "question": "ㅇ", "answer": ["이응(イウン)", "ア行", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㅁ", "answer": ["미음(ミウム)", "マ行", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㄱ", "answer": ["기역(キヨク)", "カ行", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㅅ", "answer": ["시옷(シオッ)", "サ行", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㄹ", "answer": ["리을(リウル)", "ラ行", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㄷ", "answer": ["디귿(ティグッ)", "タ行", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㄴ", "answer": ["니은(ニウン)", "ナ行", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㅂ", "answer": ["비읍(ピウプ)", "パ行", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㅎ", "answer": ["히읗(ヒウッ)", "ハ行", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㅈ", "answer": ["지읒(チウッ)", "ジャ行", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㅋ", "answer": ["키읔 キウク", "カ行（激音）", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㅌ", "answer": ["티읕 ティウッ", "タ行（激音）", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㅍ", "answer": ["피읖 ピウプ", "パ行（激音）", "子音"] },
    { "question": "ㅊ", "answer": ["치읓 チウッ", "チャ行（激音）", "子音"] },
    {
      "question": "ㄲ",
      "answer": ["쌍기역 ッサンギヨ<sub>ク</sub>", "カ行（濃音）", "子音"]
    },
    {
      "question": "ㅆ",
      "answer": ["씽시옷 ッサンシオッ", "サ行（濃音）", "子音"]
    },
    {
      "question": "ㄸ",
      "answer": ["쌍디귿 ッサンティグッ", "タ行（濃音）", "子音"]
    },
    {
      "question": "ㅃ",
      "answer": ["쌍비읍 ッサンピウ<sub>プ</sub>", "パ行（濃音）", "子音"]
    },
    {
      "question": "ㅉ",
      "answer": ["쌍지읒 ッサンチウッ", "チャ行（濃音）", "子音"]
    },
    { "question": "차", "answer": ["チャ"] },
    { "question": "파", "answer": ["パ"] },
    { "question": "타", "answer": ["タ"] },
    { "question": "카", "answer": ["カ"] },
    { "question": "짜", "answer": ["ッチャ"] },
    { "question": "빠", "answer": ["ッパ"] },
    { "question": "따", "answer": ["ッタ"] },
    { "question": "싸", "answer": ["ッサ"] },
    { "question": "까", "answer": ["ッカ"] },
    { "question": "자", "answer": ["チャ"] },
    { "question": "바", "answer": ["パ"] },
    { "question": "라", "answer": ["ラ"] },
    { "question": "마", "answer": ["マ"] },
    { "question": "하", "answer": ["ハ"] },
    { "question": "나", "answer": ["ナ"] },
    { "question": "다", "answer": ["タ"] },
    { "question": "사", "answer": ["サ"] },
    { "question": "가", "answer": ["カ"] },
    { "question": "아", "answer": ["ア"] },
    { "question": "치", "answer": ["チ"] },
    { "question": "피", "answer": ["ピ"] },
    { "question": "티", "answer": ["ティ"] },
    { "question": "키", "answer": ["キ"] },
    { "question": "찌", "answer": ["ッチ"] },
    { "question": "삐", "answer": ["ッピ"] },
    { "question": "띠", "answer": ["ッティ"] },
    { "question": "씨", "answer": ["ッシ"] },
    { "question": "끼", "answer": ["ッキ"] },
    { "question": "지", "answer": ["チ"] },
    { "question": "비", "answer": ["ピ"] },
    { "question": "리", "answer": ["リ"] },
    { "question": "미", "answer": ["ミ"] },
    { "question": "히", "answer": ["ヒ"] },
    { "question": "니", "answer": ["ニ"] },
    { "question": "디", "answer": ["ティ"] },
    { "question": "시", "answer": ["シ"] },
    { "question": "기", "answer": ["キ"] },
    { "question": "이", "answer": ["イ"] },
    { "question": "추", "answer": ["チュ"] },
    { "question": "푸", "answer": ["プ"] },
    { "question": "투", "answer": ["トゥ"] },
    { "question": "쿠", "answer": ["ク"] },
    { "question": "쭈", "answer": ["ッチュ"] },
    { "question": "뿌", "answer": ["ップ"] },
    { "question": "뚜", "answer": ["ットゥ"] },
    { "question": "쑤", "answer": ["ッス"] },
    { "question": "꾸", "answer": ["ック"] },
    { "question": "주", "answer": ["チュ"] },
    { "question": "부", "answer": ["プ"] },
    { "question": "루", "answer": ["ル"] },
    { "question": "무", "answer": ["ム"] },
    { "question": "후", "answer": ["フ"] },
    { "question": "누", "answer": ["ヌ"] },
    { "question": "두", "answer": ["トゥ"] },
    { "question": "수", "answer": ["ス"] },
    { "question": "구", "answer": ["ク"] },
    { "question": "우", "answer": ["ウ"] },
    { "question": "츠", "answer": ["チュ"] },
    { "question": "프", "answer": ["プ"] },
    { "question": "트", "answer": ["トゥ"] },
    { "question": "크", "answer": ["ク"] },
    { "question": "쯔", "answer": ["ッチュ"] },
    { "question": "쁘", "answer": ["ップ"] },
    { "question": "뜨", "answer": ["ットゥ"] },
    { "question": "쓰", "answer": ["ッス"] },
    { "question": "끄", "answer": ["ック"] },
    { "question": "즈", "answer": ["チュ"] },
    { "question": "브", "answer": ["プ"] },
    { "question": "르", "answer": ["ル"] },
    { "question": "므", "answer": ["ム"] },
    { "question": "흐", "answer": ["フ"] },
    { "question": "느", "answer": ["ヌ"] },
    { "question": "드", "answer": ["トゥ"] },
    { "question": "스", "answer": ["ス"] },
    { "question": "그", "answer": ["ク"] },
    { "question": "으", "answer": ["ウ"] },
    { "question": "채", "answer": ["チェ"] },
    { "question": "패", "answer": ["ペ"] },
    { "question": "태", "answer": ["テ"] },
    { "question": "캐", "answer": ["ケ"] },
    { "question": "째", "answer": ["ッチェ"] },
    { "question": "빼", "answer": ["ッペ"] },
    { "question": "때", "answer": ["ッテ"] },
    { "question": "쌔", "answer": ["ッセ"] },
    { "question": "깨", "answer": ["ッケ"] },
    { "question": "재", "answer": ["チェ"] },
    { "question": "배", "answer": ["ペ"] },
    { "question": "래", "answer": ["レ"] },
    { "question": "매", "answer": ["メ"] },
    { "question": "해", "answer": ["ヘ"] },
    { "question": "내", "answer": ["ネ"] },
    { "question": "대", "answer": ["テ"] },
    { "question": "새", "answer": ["セ"] },
    { "question": "개", "answer": ["ケ"] },
    { "question": "애", "answer": ["エ"] },
    { "question": "체", "answer": ["チェ"] },
    { "question": "페", "answer": ["ペ"] },
    { "question": "테", "answer": ["テ"] },
    { "question": "케", "answer": ["ケ"] },
    { "question": "쩨", "answer": ["ッチェ"] },
    { "question": "뻬", "answer": ["ッペ"] },
    { "question": "떼", "answer": ["ッテ"] },
    { "question": "쎄", "answer": ["ッセ"] },
    { "question": "께", "answer": ["ッケ"] },
    { "question": "제", "answer": ["チェ"] },
    { "question": "베", "answer": ["ペ"] },
    { "question": "레", "answer": ["レ"] },
    { "question": "메", "answer": ["メ"] },
    { "question": "헤", "answer": ["ヘ"] },
    { "question": "네", "answer": ["ネ"] },
    { "question": "데", "answer": ["テ"] },
    { "question": "세", "answer": ["セ"] },
    { "question": "게", "answer": ["ケ"] },
    { "question": "에", "answer": ["エ"] },
    { "question": "처", "answer": ["チョ"] },
    { "question": "퍼", "answer": ["ポ"] },
    { "question": "터", "answer": ["ト"] },
    { "question": "커", "answer": ["コ"] },
    { "question": "쩌", "answer": ["ッチォ"] },
    { "question": "뻐", "answer": ["ッポ"] },
    { "question": "떠", "answer": ["ット"] },
    { "question": "써", "answer": ["ッソ"] },
    { "question": "꺼", "answer": ["ッコ"] },
    { "question": "저", "answer": ["チォ"] },
    { "question": "버", "answer": ["ポ"] },
    { "question": "러", "answer": ["ロ"] },
    { "question": "머", "answer": ["モ"] },
    { "question": "허", "answer": ["ホ"] },
    { "question": "너", "answer": ["ノ"] },
    { "question": "더", "answer": ["ト"] },
    { "question": "서", "answer": ["ソ"] },
    { "question": "거", "answer": ["コ"] },
    { "question": "어", "answer": ["オ"] },
    { "question": "초", "answer": ["チョ"] },
    { "question": "포", "answer": ["ポ"] },
    { "question": "토", "answer": ["ト"] },
    { "question": "코", "answer": ["コ"] },
    { "question": "쪼", "answer": ["ッチォ"] },
    { "question": "뽀", "answer": ["ッポ"] },
    { "question": "또", "answer": ["ット"] },
    { "question": "쏘", "answer": ["ッソ"] },
    { "question": "꼬", "answer": ["ッコ"] },
    { "question": "조", "answer": ["チォ"] },
    { "question": "보", "answer": ["ポ"] },
    { "question": "로", "answer": ["ロ"] },
    { "question": "모", "answer": ["モ"] },
    { "question": "호", "answer": ["ホ"] },
    { "question": "노", "answer": ["ノ"] },
    { "question": "도", "answer": ["ト"] },
    { "question": "소", "answer": ["ソ"] },
    { "question": "고", "answer": ["コ"] },
    { "question": "오", "answer": ["オ"] },
    { "question": "챠", "answer": ["チャ"] },
    { "question": "퍄", "answer": ["ピャ"] },
    { "question": "탸", "answer": ["ティャ"] },
    { "question": "캬", "answer": ["キャ"] },
    { "question": "쨔", "answer": ["ッチャ"] },
    { "question": "뺘", "answer": ["ッピャ"] },
    { "question": "땨", "answer": ["ッティャ"] },
    { "question": "쌰", "answer": ["ッシャ"] },
    { "question": "꺄", "answer": ["ッキャ"] },
    { "question": "쟈", "answer": ["チャ"] },
    { "question": "뱌", "answer": ["ピャ"] },
    { "question": "랴", "answer": ["リャ"] },
    { "question": "먀", "answer": ["ミャ"] },
    { "question": "햐", "answer": ["ヒャ"] },
    { "question": "냐", "answer": ["ニャ"] },
    { "question": "댜", "answer": ["ティヤ"] },
    { "question": "샤", "answer": ["シャ"] },
    { "question": "갸", "answer": ["キャ"] },
    { "question": "야", "answer": ["ヤ"] },
    { "question": "츄", "answer": ["チュ"] },
    { "question": "퓨", "answer": ["ピュ"] },
    { "question": "튜", "answer": ["テュ"] },
    { "question": "큐", "answer": ["キュ"] },
    { "question": "쮸", "answer": ["ッチュ"] },
    { "question": "쀼", "answer": ["ッピュ"] },
    { "question": "뜌", "answer": ["ッテュ"] },
    { "question": "쓔", "answer": ["ッシュ"] },
    { "question": "뀨", "answer": ["ッキュ"] },
    { "question": "쥬", "answer": ["チュ"] },
    { "question": "뷰", "answer": ["ピュ"] },
    { "question": "류", "answer": ["リュ"] },
    { "question": "뮤", "answer": ["ミュ"] },
    { "question": "휴", "answer": ["ヒュ"] },
    { "question": "뉴", "answer": ["ニュ"] },
    { "question": "듀", "answer": ["テュ"] },
    { "question": "슈", "answer": ["シュ"] },
    { "question": "규", "answer": ["キュ"] },
    { "question": "유", "answer": ["ユ"] },
    { "question": "쳐", "answer": ["チョ"] },
    { "question": "펴", "answer": ["ピョ"] },
    { "question": "텨", "answer": ["ティョ"] },
    { "question": "켜", "answer": ["キョ"] },
    { "question": "쪄", "answer": ["ッチョ"] },
    { "question": "뼈", "answer": ["ッピョ"] },
    { "question": "뗘", "answer": ["ッティョ"] },
    { "question": "쎠", "answer": ["ッショ"] },
    { "question": "껴", "answer": ["ッキョ"] },
    { "question": "져", "answer": ["チョ"] },
    { "question": "벼", "answer": ["ピョ"] },
    { "question": "려", "answer": ["リョ"] },
    { "question": "며", "answer": ["ミョ"] },
    { "question": "혀", "answer": ["ヒョ"] },
    { "question": "녀", "answer": ["ニョ"] },
    { "question": "뎌", "answer": ["ティョ"] },
    { "question": "셔", "answer": ["ショ"] },
    { "question": "겨", "answer": ["キョ"] },
    { "question": "여", "answer": ["ヨ"] },
    { "question": "쵸", "answer": ["チョ"] },
    { "question": "표", "answer": ["ピョ"] },
    { "question": "툐", "answer": ["ティョ"] },
    { "question": "쿄", "answer": ["キョ"] },
    { "question": "쬬", "answer": ["ッチョ"] },
    { "question": "뾰", "answer": ["ッピョ"] },
    { "question": "뚀", "answer": ["ッティョ"] },
    { "question": "쑈", "answer": ["ッショ"] },
    { "question": "꾜", "answer": ["ッキョ"] },
    { "question": "죠", "answer": ["チョ"] },
    { "question": "뵤", "answer": ["ピョ"] },
    { "question": "료", "answer": ["リョ"] },
    { "question": "묘", "answer": ["ミョ"] },
    { "question": "효", "answer": ["ヒョ"] },
    { "question": "뇨", "answer": ["ニョ"] },
    { "question": "됴", "answer": ["ティョ"] },
    { "question": "쇼", "answer": ["ショ"] },
    { "question": "교", "answer": ["キョ"] },
    { "question": "요", "answer": ["ヨ"] },
    { "question": "촤", "answer": ["チョヮ"] },
    { "question": "퐈", "answer": ["ポヮ"] },
    { "question": "톼", "answer": ["トヮ"] },
    { "question": "콰", "answer": ["コヮ"] },
    { "question": "쫘", "answer": ["ッチョヮ"] },
    { "question": "뽜", "answer": ["ッポヮ"] },
    { "question": "똬", "answer": ["ットヮ"] },
    { "question": "쏴", "answer": ["ッソヮ"] },
    { "question": "꽈", "answer": ["ッコヮ"] },
    { "question": "좌", "answer": ["チョヮ"] },
    { "question": "봐", "answer": ["ポヮ"] },
    { "question": "롸", "answer": ["ロヮ"] },
    { "question": "뫄", "answer": ["モヮ"] },
    { "question": "화", "answer": ["ホヮ"] },
    { "question": "놔", "answer": ["ノヮ"] },
    { "question": "돠", "answer": ["トヮ"] },
    { "question": "솨", "answer": ["ソヮ"] },
    { "question": "과", "answer": ["コヮ"] },
    { "question": "와", "answer": ["ワ"] },
    { "question": "챼", "answer": ["チィェ"] },
    { "question": "퍠", "answer": ["ピィェ"] },
    { "question": "턔", "answer": ["ティェ"] },
    { "question": "컈", "answer": ["キィェ"] },
    { "question": "쨰", "answer": ["ッチィェ"] },
    { "question": "뺴", "answer": ["ッピィェ"] },
    { "question": "떄", "answer": ["ッティェ"] },
    { "question": "썌", "answer": ["ッシィェ"] },
    { "question": "꺠", "answer": ["ッキィェ"] },
    { "question": "쟤", "answer": ["チィェ"] },
    { "question": "뱨", "answer": ["ピィェ"] },
    { "question": "럐", "answer": ["リィェ"] },
    { "question": "먜", "answer": ["ミィェ"] },
    { "question": "햬", "answer": ["ヒィェ"] },
    { "question": "냬", "answer": ["ニィェ"] },
    { "question": "댸", "answer": ["ティェ"] },
    { "question": "섀", "answer": ["シィェ"] },
    { "question": "걔", "answer": ["キィェ"] },
    { "question": "얘", "answer": ["イェ"] },
    { "question": "쳬", "answer": ["チェェ"] },
    { "question": "폐", "answer": ["ペェ"] },
    { "question": "톄", "answer": ["テェ"] },
    { "question": "켸", "answer": ["ケェ"] },
    { "question": "쪠", "answer": ["ッチェェ"] },
    { "question": "뼤", "answer": ["ッペェ"] },
    { "question": "뗴", "answer": ["ッテェ"] },
    { "question": "쎼", "answer": ["ッシェェ"] },
    { "question": "꼐", "answer": ["ッケェ"] },
    { "question": "졔", "answer": ["チェェ"] },
    { "question": "볘", "answer": ["ペェ"] },
    { "question": "례", "answer": ["レェ"] },
    { "question": "몌", "answer": ["メェ"] },
    { "question": "혜", "answer": ["ヘェ"] },
    { "question": "녜", "answer": ["ネェ"] },
    { "question": "뎨", "answer": ["テェ"] },
    { "question": "셰", "answer": ["シェェ"] },
    { "question": "계", "answer": ["ケェ"] },
    { "question": "예", "answer": ["イェ"] },
    { "question": "취", "answer": ["チュィ"] },
    { "question": "퓌", "answer": ["プィ"] },
    { "question": "튀", "answer": ["トゥィ"] },
    { "question": "퀴", "answer": ["クィ"] },
    { "question": "쮜", "answer": ["ッチュィ"] },
    { "question": "쀠", "answer": ["ップィ"] },
    { "question": "뛰", "answer": ["ットゥィ"] },
    { "question": "쒸", "answer": ["ッスィ"] },
    { "question": "뀌", "answer": ["ックィ"] },
    { "question": "쥐", "answer": ["チュィ"] },
    { "question": "뷔", "answer": ["プィ"] },
    { "question": "뤼", "answer": ["ルィ"] },
    { "question": "뮈", "answer": ["ムィ"] },
    { "question": "휘", "answer": ["フィ"] },
    { "question": "뉘", "answer": ["ヌィ"] },
    { "question": "뒤", "answer": ["トゥィ"] },
    { "question": "쉬", "answer": ["スィ"] },
    { "question": "귀", "answer": ["クィ"] },
    { "question": "위", "answer": ["ウィ"] },
    { "question": "츼", "answer": ["チュィ"] },
    { "question": "픠", "answer": ["プィ"] },
    { "question": "틔", "answer": ["トゥィ"] },
    { "question": "킈", "answer": ["クィ"] },
    { "question": "쯰", "answer": ["ッチュィ"] },
    { "question": "쁴", "answer": ["ップィ"] },
    { "question": "띄", "answer": ["ットゥィ"] },
    { "question": "씌", "answer": ["ッスィ"] },
    { "question": "끠", "answer": ["ックィ"] },
    { "question": "즤", "answer": ["チュィ"] },
    { "question": "븨", "answer": ["プィ"] },
    { "question": "릐", "answer": ["ルィ"] },
    { "question": "믜", "answer": ["ムィ"] },
    { "question": "희", "answer": ["フィ"] },
    { "question": "늬", "answer": ["ヌィ"] },
    { "question": "듸", "answer": ["トゥィ"] },
    { "question": "싀", "answer": ["スィ"] },
    { "question": "긔", "answer": ["クィ"] },
    { "question": "의", "answer": ["ウィ"] },
    { "question": "쵀", "answer": ["チュェ"] },
    { "question": "퐤", "answer": ["プェ"] },
    { "question": "퇘", "answer": ["トゥェ"] },
    { "question": "쾌", "answer": ["クェ"] },
    { "question": "쫴", "answer": ["ッチュェ"] },
    { "question": "뽸", "answer": ["ップェ"] },
    { "question": "뙈", "answer": ["ットゥェ"] },
    { "question": "쐐", "answer": ["ッスェ"] },
    { "question": "꽤", "answer": ["ックェ"] },
    { "question": "좨", "answer": ["チュェ"] },
    { "question": "봬", "answer": ["プェ"] },
    { "question": "뢔", "answer": ["ルェ"] },
    { "question": "뫠", "answer": ["ムェ"] },
    { "question": "홰", "answer": ["フェ"] },
    { "question": "놰", "answer": ["ヌェ"] },
    { "question": "돼", "answer": ["トゥェ"] },
    { "question": "쇄", "answer": ["スェ"] },
    { "question": "괘", "answer": ["クェ"] },
    { "question": "왜", "answer": ["ウェ"] },
    { "question": "최", "answer": ["チュェ"] },
    { "question": "푀", "answer": ["プェ"] },
    { "question": "퇴", "answer": ["トゥェ"] },
    { "question": "쾨", "answer": ["クェ"] },
    { "question": "쬐", "answer": ["ッチュェ"] },
    { "question": "뾔", "answer": ["ップェ"] },
    { "question": "뙤", "answer": ["ットゥェ"] },
    { "question": "쐬", "answer": ["ッスェ"] },
    { "question": "꾀", "answer": ["ックェ"] },
    { "question": "죄", "answer": ["チュェ"] },
    { "question": "뵈", "answer": ["プェ"] },
    { "question": "뢰", "answer": ["ルェ"] },
    { "question": "뫼", "answer": ["ムェ"] },
    { "question": "회", "answer": ["フェ"] },
    { "question": "뇌", "answer": ["ヌェ"] },
    { "question": "되", "answer": ["トゥェ"] },
    { "question": "쇠", "answer": ["スェ"] },
    { "question": "괴", "answer": ["クェ"] },
    { "question": "외", "answer": ["ウェ"] },
    { "question": "췌", "answer": ["チュェ"] },
    { "question": "풰", "answer": ["プェ"] },
    { "question": "퉤", "answer": ["トゥェ"] },
    { "question": "퀘", "answer": ["クェ"] },
    { "question": "쮀", "answer": ["ッチュェ"] },
    { "question": "쀄", "answer": ["ップェ"] },
    { "question": "뛔", "answer": ["ットゥェ"] },
    { "question": "쒜", "answer": ["ッスェ"] },
    { "question": "꿰", "answer": ["ックェ"] },
    { "question": "줴", "answer": ["チュェ"] },
    { "question": "붸", "answer": ["プェ"] },
    { "question": "뤠", "answer": ["ルェ"] },
    { "question": "뭬", "answer": ["ムェ"] },
    { "question": "훼", "answer": ["フェ"] },
    { "question": "눼", "answer": ["ヌェ"] },
    { "question": "뒈", "answer": ["トゥェ"] },
    { "question": "쉐", "answer": ["スェ"] },
    { "question": "궤", "answer": ["クェ"] },
    { "question": "웨", "answer": ["ウェ"] },
    { "question": "춰", "answer": ["チュォ"] },
    { "question": "풔", "answer": ["プォ"] },
    { "question": "퉈", "answer": ["トゥォ"] },
    { "question": "쿼", "answer": ["クォ"] },
    { "question": "쭤", "answer": ["ッチュォ"] },
    { "question": "뿨", "answer": ["ップォ"] },
    { "question": "뚸", "answer": ["ットゥォ"] },
    { "question": "쒀", "answer": ["ッスォ"] },
    { "question": "궈", "answer": ["ックォ"] },
    { "question": "줘", "answer": ["チュォ"] },
    { "question": "붜", "answer": ["プォ"] },
    { "question": "뤄", "answer": ["ルォ"] },
    { "question": "뭐", "answer": ["ムォ"] },
    { "question": "훠", "answer": ["フォ"] },
    { "question": "눠", "answer": ["ヌォ"] },
    { "question": "둬", "answer": ["トゥォ"] },
    { "question": "숴", "answer": ["スォ"] },
    { "question": "궈", "answer": ["クォ"] },
    { "question": "워", "answer": ["ウォ"] }
  ]
}
